Pattaraporn Padmasakul (Mook)

9/577 Ideo Mix Udomsuk, Sukhumvit 103, Bangna, Bangkok 10260

Mobile 089 605 2929

Email pattaraporn.pad@gmail.com

Age 26

Expected Salary 60,000 THB

PERSONAL OBJECTIVE:

I have self-motivated, ambitious, and love to learn new things. I am not frustrated when I cannot reach target or they want me to build a new team but I try to solve it and make team achieve the goal. I have born to be Sales and Business Development person. I search for a challenging opportunity with the reputable company in order to effectively apply the theories in class and allexperiences with the real business world to produce results for the team and the organization.

CORE STRENGTHS:

- Ability and desire to sell and negotiate
- Excellent communication skills
- Ability to work under the pressure
- Skill to work both independently and as part of a team
- Proficient in Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Photoshop, and Using Internet
- Analyze by database and Google Analytic
- Fluency in Thai and good command in English

Pattaraporn Padmasakul (Mook)

WORK EXPERIENCES

SHOPSEASON Co.,Ltd.

Sales Executive: Business Development (March 2016 to present)

- SEASON's only Sales Executive
- Find partners to work with **SEASON** and analyze the mechanics for partnership including local brands, global brands, and Thai designer brands
- Make an appointments for meetings and create presentations for partners
- Dealing with the partner about the promotion, cost, channel to promote business
- Follow the process of each partner from start until finish
- Report to the CEOs regarding partnerships
- Participate in meetings with potential partners

ZALORA (THAILAND) Co.,Ltd.

Partnership Manager: Marketing Department, (March 2015 to September 2015)

- Find partners to work with **ZALORA** and analyze the mechanics for partnership
- Make an appointments for meetings and create presentations for partners
- Dealing with the partner about the promotion, cost, channel to promote business
- Follow the process of each partner from start until finish
- Do the report to partner and show the presentation to VP of Marketing
- Analyze the channel that company can gain the most customers
- Collecting document and keep it as secret of company
- Solving the problems of partners and customers

LAZADA (THAILAND) Co.,Ltd.

Account Manager: Sales and Partnership Department, (December 2014 to March 2015)

- Find strong partners to work with LAZADA and mechanic deals for campaign use
- Mock up graphics, generate voucher code for partners and choose channels for campaign
- Analyze and summarize the report to the Managing Director of LAZADA and Partners
- Summarize the report for meeting both inside and outside company
- Find solution to continue work with partners and control the process in the team

Pattaraporn Padmasakul (Mook)

Business Development Assistant: Sales and Business Development Department, (March to November 2014)

- Find sellers to join in marketplace; invite them to be a seller on the LAZADA website
- Train sellers to manage LAZADA's system and help them to do the marketing and promotion
- Summarize the report to the manager
- Find solutions to increase sales volume

EDUCATION AND ACTIVITIES

Assumption University - Bangkok, Thailand (March2009-October 2013) Bachelor of Business Administration

Marketing and Minor Strategic Major

- Staff of ABAC Students Affairs
- Secretary of Oratory and Personality Club
- Volunteer teacher at Wangtago School, Chonburi

AWARDS:

Certificated of Speech in the topic "MY KING" (2009, Assumption University)

ACHIEVEMENTS:

Most Sellers Lived Thailand 2014: LAZADA

GOAL

- To grow together with the company
- To led the company is the leader in the market
- To be a professional in my career
- To feel stable to work in the company
- To be a value in the company